<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric Eskildsen&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eric Eskildsen&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:38:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Enough Software Architecture: Chapter 3</title>
      <link>/posts/just-enough-software-architecture-chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/just-enough-software-architecture-chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>This series loosely summarizes George Fairbanks&amp;rsquo;s Just Enough Software Architecture: A Risk-Driven Approach as I read through it.
 Chapter 3 of Just Enough Software Architecture details the how of the risk-driven model. How should it be applied? What techniques should be used?
Are You Risk-Driven? Some teams think they&amp;rsquo;re already risk-driven when they&amp;rsquo;re not. How can you know for sure?
Look at your processes. Do you have rigid rules?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Ubuntu Setup</title>
      <link>/posts/documenting-my-ubuntu-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:19:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/documenting-my-ubuntu-setup/</guid>
      <description>This post is a work in progress.
 I switched from Windows to Ubuntu as my daily driver a couple months ago. It&amp;rsquo;s been great fun and a great learning experience. At this point, I&amp;rsquo;ve customized it so much that I figured I should create a knowledge dump for reference when starting from scratch.
Desktop Environment and Window Manager I use i3 on top of Xfce. There&amp;rsquo;s overlap, but they serve different purposes for me:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Enough Software Architecture: Chapter 1</title>
      <link>/posts/just-enough-software-architecture-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:25:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/just-enough-software-architecture-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>This series loosely summarizes George Fairbanks&amp;rsquo;s Just Enough Software Architecture: A Risk-Driven Approach as I read through it.
 Intro Software is getting harder. It may be the most complicated thing humans have ever built. Consequently, we need tools to approach it with.
3 Tools To Approach Software With  Partitioning: Separate parts of a project. This lets you forget about the details. &amp;ldquo;I have a thousand classes in this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching From Windows to Ubuntu as My Daily Driver</title>
      <link>/posts/switching-from-windows-to-ubuntu-as-my-daily-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 10:34:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/switching-from-windows-to-ubuntu-as-my-daily-driver/</guid>
      <description>About a week ago, I started using Ubuntu as my daily driver instead of Windows. This post explains why and (partially) documents my setup &amp;hellip; mostly to jog my memory when I forget half of what I did, but hopefully someone else considering a similar setup will benefit too.
Why Not Windows 10? I like Windows. PowerShell is a fantastic abstraction of .NET, and now that it&amp;rsquo;s cross platform, I&amp;rsquo;ll be using it on Linux too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>